<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!--
!!!DO NOT EDIT. THIS FILE IS GENERATED BY CODE AND ANY CHANGES MAY BE OVERWRITTEN!!!
-->
<rdf:RDF xmlns:rdf="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#" xmlns:kc="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/configuration/" xmlns:mso="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/">
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.ampere">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">The ampere (SI unit symbol: A), often shortened to amp, is the SI unit of electric current (quantity symbol: I,i) and is one of the seven SI base units. It is named after Andr??-Marie Amp??re (1775???1836), French mathematician and physicist, considered the father of electrodynamics. Note that SI supports only the use of symbols and deprecates the use of any abbreviations for units.\nIn practical terms, the ampere is a measure of the amount of electric charge passing a point in an electric circuit per unit time with 6.241??????10 electrons, or one coulomb per second constituting one ampere.\nThe practical definition may lead to confusion with the definition of a coulomb (i.e., 1 amp-second), but in practical terms this means that measures of a constant current (e.g., the nominal flow of charge per second through a simple circuit) will be defined in amperes (e.g., "a 20 mA circuit") and the flow of charge through a circuit over a period of time will be defined in coulombs (e.g., "a variable-current circuit that flows a total of 10 coulombs over 5 seconds"). In this way, amperes can be viewed as a flow rate, i.e. number of particles (charged) transiting per unit time, and coulombs simply as</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Ampere</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.ampere_per_hour">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">Enumeration representing the ampere-hour or amp-hour, which is a unit of electric charge.</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Ampere per Hour</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.ampere_per_joule">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">Enumeration for the unit ampere per joule.</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Ampere per Joule</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.ampere_per_metre">
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Ampere per metre</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.ampere_per_square_metre">
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Ampere per square metre</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.astronomical_unit">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">A unit for measuring vast distances in space.  Approximately equal to the distance from the Earth to the Sun, it is precisely defined as 149597870700 meters (about 150 million kilometers, or 93 million miles).</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Astronomical Unit</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.atomic_mass_unit">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">The unified atomic mass unit (also known as amu, symbol: u) or dalton (symbol: Da) is the standard unit that is used for indicating mass on an atomic or molecular scale (atomic mass). It is defined as one twelfth of the rest mass of an unbound neutral atom of carbon-12 in its nuclear and electronic ground state, and has a value of 1.660538921(73)??10??kg. One dalton is approximately equal to the mass of one proton or one neutron; an equivalence of saying 1 g mol. The CIPM have categorised it as a "non-SI unit" because units values in SI units must be obtained experimentally.\nThe atomic weight scale has traditionally been a relative scale, that is without an explicit unit, with the first atomic weight basis suggested by John Dalton in 1803 as H. Despite the initial mass of H being used as the natural unit for atomic weight, it was suggested by Wilhelm Ostwald that atomic weights would be best expressed in terms in units of 1/16 weight of oxygen. This evaluation was made prior to the discovery of the existence of elemental isotopes, which occurred in 1912.\nThe discovery of isotopic oxygen in 1929 led to a divergence in atomic weight representation, with isotopically weighted oxygen</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Atomic mass unit</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.bar">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">The bar is a unit of pressure defined as 1,000,000 dynes per square centimetre (or equivalently in SI units, 100 kilopascals, or in CGS units, 1 megabarye). It is about equal to the atmospheric pressure on Earth at sea level.\nOther units derived from the bar are the megabar (symbol: Mbar), kilobar (symbol: kbar), decibar (symbol: dbar), centibar (symbol: cbar), and millibar (symbol: mbar or mb). They are not SI units, nor are they cgs units, but they are accepted for use with the SI. The bar is widely used in descriptions of pressure because it is only about 1% smaller than the atmosphere (symbol: atm), which now is defined to be 1.01325??bar exactly. The bar is legally recognized in countries of the European Union.\nIn 1985 the IUPAC recommended that the standard for atmospheric pressure should be harmonized to 100,000??Pa = 1??bar = 750??Torr. The same definition is used in the compressor and the pneumatic tool industries (ISO 2787).\nThe bar and the millibar were introduced by the British meteorologist William Napier Shaw in 1909. He was the director of the Meteorological Office in London from 1907 to 1920.\nBarg is a unit of gauge pressure, i.e., pressure in bars above ambient or</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Bar</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.baud">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">In telecommunications and electronics, baud (/??b????d/, unit symbol "Bd") is synonymous to symbols per second or pulses per second. It is the unit of symbol rate, also known as baud rate or modulation rate; the number of distinct symbol changes (signaling events) made to the transmission medium per second in a digitally modulated signal or a line code. The baud rate is related to but should not be confused with gross bit rate expressed in bit/s.\nThe symbol duration time, also known as unit interval, can be directly measured as the time between transitions by looking into an eye diagram of an oscilloscope. The symbol duration time Ts can be calculated as:\nwhere fs is the symbol rate.\nIn digital systems (uses discrete/discontinuous values) with binary code 1 Bd = 1 bit/s. By contrast, non-digital (or analog) systems use a continuous range of values to represent information and in these systems the exact informational size of 1 Bd varies.\nThe baud unit is named after ??mile Baudot, the inventor of the Baudot code for telegraphy, and is represented as SI units. That is, the first letter of its symbol is uppercase (Bd), but when the unit is spelled out, it should be written in lowercase</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Baud</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.beats_per_minute">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">An enumeration for measuring a quantity by beats per minute. This unit of measurement can be used to measure heart rates or music tempo.</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Beats per Minute</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.becquerel">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">The becquerel (symbol Bq) (pronounced: 'be-k??-rel) is the SI-derived unit of radioactivity. One Bq is defined as the activity of a quantity of radioactive material in which one nucleus decays per second. The Bq unit is therefore equivalent to an inverse second, s. The becquerel is named for Henri Becquerel, who shared a Nobel Prize with Pierre and Marie Curie in 1903 for their work in discovering radioactivity.\nIn a fixed mass of radioactive material, the number of becquerels changes with time. Therefore, a sample radioactive decay rate is stated with a timestamp for short-lived isotopes, sometimes after adjustment to some specific date of interest (in the past or in the future). For example, one might quote a ten-day adjusted figure, that is, the amount of radioactivity that will still be present ten days in the future. This can de-emphasize short-lived isotopes. The average human body has 4400 becquerels from decaying potassium-40, which is a naturally-occurring isotope of potassium.\nExpressing the number of decays per second rather than the mean time between decays avoids the confusing situation that a lower number represents more radioactivity.\nAs any SI unit, Bq can be</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Becquerel</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.bit_per_second">
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">bit per second</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.bohr_magneton">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">In atomic physics, the Bohr magneton (symbol ??B) is a physical constant and the natural unit for expressing an electron magnetic dipole moment. The Bohr magneton is defined in SI units by\nand in Gaussian CGS units by\nwhere\nThe magnitude of an electron's spin magnetic moment is approximately one Bohr magneton.\nThe idea of elementary magnets is due to Walter Ritz (1907) and Pierre Weiss. Already before the Rutherford model of atomic structure, several theorists commented that the magneton should involve Planck's constant h. By postulating that the ratio of electron kinetic energy to orbital frequency should be equal to h, Richard Gans computed a value that was twice as large as the Bohr magneton in September 1911. At the First Solvay Conference in November that year, Paul Langevin obtained a submultiple. The Romanian physicist ??tefan Procopiu obtained for the first time its value in 1911; the value is referred to as the "Bohr???Procopiu magneton" in Romanian scientific literature.\nThe Bohr magneton is the magnitude of the magnetic dipole moment of an orbiting electron with an orbital angular momentum of one ??. According to the Bohr model, this is the ground state, i.e. the state of</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Bohr magneton</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.btus_per_hour">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">An enumeration value indicating the unit of British Thermal Units per hour.</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">BTUs per Hour</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.byte">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">The byte (??/??ba??t/) is a unit of digital information in computing and telecommunications that most commonly consists of eight bits. Historically, a byte was the number of bits used to encode a single character of text in a computer and for this reason it is the basic addressable element in many computer architectures. The size of the byte has historically been hardware dependent and no definitive standards existed that mandated the size. The de facto standard of eight bits is a convenient power of two permitting the values 0 through 255 for one byte. With ISO/IEC 80000-13, this common meaning was codified in a formal standard. Many types of applications use variables representable in eight or fewer bits, and processor designers optimize for this common usage. The popularity of major commercial computing architectures have aided in the ubiquitous acceptance of the 8-bit size.\nThe term octet was defined to explicitly denote a sequence of 8 bits because of the ambiguity associated at the time with the term byte.\nThe term byte was coined by Dr. Werner Buchholz in July 1956, during the early design phase for the IBM Stretch computer. It is a deliberate respelling of bite to avoid</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Byte</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.calendar_year">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">Generally speaking, a calendar year begins on the New Year's Day of the given calendar system and ends on the day before the following New Year's Day. By convention, a calendar year consists of a natural number of days. </mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Year</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.calory">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">The Calory is a metric system unit of energy.</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Calory</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.candela">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">The candela (??/k??n??d??l??/ or /k??n??di??l??/; symbol: cd) is the SI base unit of luminous intensity; that is, power emitted by a light source in a particular direction, weighted by the luminosity function (a standardized model of the sensitivity of the human eye to different wavelengths, also known as the luminous efficiency function). A common candle emits light with a luminous intensity of roughly one candela. If emission in some directions is blocked by an opaque barrier, the emission would still be approximately one candela in the directions that are not obscured.\nThe word candela means candle in Latin, as well as in many modern languages.\nLike other SI base units, the candela has an operational definition???it is defined by a description of a physical process that will produce one candela of luminous intensity. Since the 16th General Conference on Weights and Measures??(CGPM) in 1979, the candela has been defined as:\nThe candela is the luminous intensity, in a given direction, of a source that emits monochromatic radiation of frequency 540??10??hertz and that has a radiant intensity in that direction of ???683??watt per steradian.\nThe definition describes how to produce a light source that</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Candela</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.candela_per_square_metre">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">The candela per square metre (cd/m) is the derived SI unit of luminance. The unit is based on the candela, the SI unit of luminous intensity, and the square metre, the SI unit of area. Nit (nt) is a deprecated non-SI name also used for this unit (1 nit = 1??cd/m).\nAs a measure of light emitted per unit area, this unit is frequently used to specify the brightness of a display device. Most consumer desktop liquid crystal displays have luminances of 200 to 300??cd/m; the sRGB spec for monitors targets 80??cd/m. HDTVs range from 450 to about 1000??cd/m. Typically, calibrated monitors should have a brightness of 120??cd/m.\nNit is believed to come from the Latin word nitere, to shine.\nOne candela per square metre is equal to:</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Candela per square metre</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.celsius">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">Celsius, also known as centigrade, is a scale and unit of measurement for temperature. It is named after the Swedish astronomer Anders Celsius (1701???1744), who developed a similar temperature scale. The degree Celsius (??C) can refer to a specific temperature on the Celsius scale as well as a unit to indicate a temperature interval, a difference between two temperatures or an uncertainty. The unit was known until 1948 as "centigrade" from the Latin centum translated as 100 and gradus translated as "steps".\nFrom 1744 until 1954, 0????C was defined as the freezing point of water and 100????C was defined as the boiling point of water, both at a pressure of one standard atmosphere with mercury being the working material. Although these defining correlations are commonly taught in schools today, by international agreement the unit "degree Celsius" and the Celsius scale are currently defined by two different temperatures: absolute zero, and the triple point of VSMOW (specially-purified water). This definition also precisely relates the Celsius scale to the Kelvin scale, which defines the SI base unit of thermodynamic temperature with symbol K. Absolute zero, the lowest temperature possible at</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Degree Celsius</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.centimeter">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">A centimetre (American spelling: centimeter, symbol cm) is a unit of length in the metric system, equal to one hundredth of a metre, which is the SI base unit of length. Centi is the SI prefix for a factor of 10. Hence a centimetre can be written as 10??10??m (engineering notation) or 1E???2??m (scientific E notation) ??? meaning 10??mm or 1??m/100 respectively. The centimetre is the base unit of length in the now deprecated centimetre-gram-second (CGS) system of units.\nThough for many physical quantities, SI prefixes for factors of 10???like milli- and kilo-???are often preferred by technicians, the centimetre remains a practical unit of length for many everyday measurements. A centimetre is approximately the width of the fingernail of an adult person (between 3/8 in and 7/16 inch on an English inch ruler).\n1 centimetre is equal to:\n1 cubic centimetre is equal to 1 millilitre, under the current SI system of units.\nIn addition to its use in the measurement of length, the centimetre is used:\nFor the purposes of compatibility with Chinese, Japanese and Korean (CJK) characters, Unicode has symbols for:\nThey are mostly used only with East Asian fixed-width CJK fonts, because they are equal in size</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Centimeter</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.coulomb">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">The coulomb (symbol: C) is the SI derived unit of electric charge. It is defined as the charge transported by a steady current of one ampere in one second:\nOne coulomb is also the amount of excess charge on the positive side of a capacitance of one farad charged to a potential difference of one volt:\nThis SI unit is named after Charles-Augustin de Coulomb. As with every International System of Units (SI) unit whose name is derived from the proper name of a person, the first letter of its symbol is upper case (C). When an SI unit is spelled out in English, it should always begin with a lower case letter (coulomb), except where any word would be capitalized, such as at the beginning of a sentence or in capitalized material such as a title. Note that "degree Celsius" conforms to this rule because the "d" is lowercase. ???Based on The International System of Units, section 5.2.\nIn the SI system, the coulomb is defined in terms of the ampere and second: 1C = 1A ?? 1s. The second is defined in terms of a frequency which is naturally emitted by caesium atoms. The ampere is defined using Amp??re's force law; the definition relies in part on the mass of the international prototype kilogram, a</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Coulomb</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.coulomb_meter">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">Enumeration for the unit coulomb meter.</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Coulomb Meter</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.coulomb_per_cubic_metre">
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Coulomb per cubic metre</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.coulomb_per_kilogram">
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Coulomb per kilogram</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.coulomb_per_mole">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">Enumeration for the unit coulomb per mole.</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">C/mol</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.coulomb_per_square_metre">
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Coulomb per square metre</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.cubic_foot">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">The cubic foot is an Imperial and US customary (non-metric) unit of volume, used in the United States and the United Kingdom. It is defined as the volume of a cube with sides of one foot (0.3048 m) in length. To calculate cubic feet multiply length X width X height.\nThere is no universally agreed symbol but the following are used:\nThere is no universally agreed symbol but the following are used:\nThere is no universally agreed symbol but the following are used:\nA standard cubic foot (abbreviated scf) is a measure of quantity of gas, sometimes but not always defined as a cubic foot of volume at 60 degrees Fahrenheit and 14.7 pounds per square inch (PSI) of pressure. See standard temperature and pressure.</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Cubic foot</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.cubic_inch">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">Unit of measure of cubic inch</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Cubic Inch</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.cubic_kilometer">
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Cubic kilometer</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.cubic_meter_per_kilogram_per_second_squared">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">Enumeration for the unit cubic meter per kilogram per second squared.</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">m^3kg^-1s^-2</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.cubic_metre">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">The cubic metre (US spelling: cubic meter, symbol: m) is the SI derived unit of volume. It is the volume of a cube with edges one metre in length. An alternative name, which allowed a different usage with metric prefixes, was the st??re. Another alternative name, not widely used any more, is the kilolitre.\n1 cubic metre is equivalent to:\nA cubic metre of pure water at the temperature of maximum density (3.98 ??C) and standard atmospheric pressure (101.325 kPa) has a mass of 1,000 kg, or one tonne. At 0 ??C, the freezing point of water, it is slightly less, 999.972 kilograms.\nIt is sometimes abbreviated to cu m, m3, M3, m^3, m**3, CBM, cbm when superscript characters or markup cannot be used (e.g. in some typewritten documents and postings in Usenet newsgroups).\nAbbreviated CBM and cbm in the freight business and MTQ (or numeric code 49) in international trade.\nSee 1 E-3 m?? for a comparison with other volumes.</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Cubic metre</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.cubic_metre_per_kilogram">
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Cubic metre per kilogram</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.cubic_metre_per_mole">
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Cubic metre per mole</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.cubic_metres_per_second">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">A cubic metre per second (m???s, m/s, cumecs or cubic meter per second in American English) is a derived SI unit of flow rate equal to that of a stere or cube with sides of one metre (~39.37 in) in length exchanged or moving each second. It is popularly used for water flow, especially in rivers and streams, and fractions for HVAC values measuring air flow.\n1 cubic metre per second is the same as:</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Cubic metres per second</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.cup_volume_measure">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">A widely used measure of volume in the United States.  It is equal to 8 fluid ounces, one half of pint, and one quarter of a quart. </mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Cup Volume</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.day">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">A day is a unit of time, commonly defined as an interval equal to 24 hours.</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Day</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.decibel">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">A unit used to measure the intensity of a sound by comparing it with a given level on a logarithmic scale.</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Decibel</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.degree">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">A degree (in full, a degree of arc, arc degree, or arcdegree), usually denoted by ?? (the degree symbol), is a measurement of plane angle, representing ???360 of a full rotation; one degree is equivalent to ??/180 radians. It is not an SI unit, as the SI unit for angles is radian, but it is mentioned in the SI brochure as an accepted unit.\nThe original motivation for choosing the degree as a unit of rotations and angles is unknown. One theory states that it is related to the fact that 360 is approximately the number of days in a year. Ancient astronomers noticed that the sun, that follows through the ecliptic path over the course of the year, seems to advance in that path by approximately one degree, each day. Some ancient calendars, such as the Persian calendar, used 360 days for a year. The Mayans used 20 cycles of 18 plus 5 unlucky days in one of their Maya calendars. The use of a calendar with 360 days may be related to the use of sexagesimal numbers.\nAnother theory is that the Babylonians subdivided the circle using the angle of an equilateral triangle as the basic unit and further subdivided the latter into 60 parts following their sexagesimal numeric system. The earliest</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Degree</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.electronvolt">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">In physics, the electron volt (symbol eV; also written electronvolt) is a unit of energy equal to approximately 1.6??10 joule (symbol J). By definition, it is the amount of energy gained by the charge of a single electron moved across an electric potential difference of one volt. Thus it is 1 volt (1 joule per coulomb, 1 J/C) multiplied by the electron charge (1??e, or 1.602176565(35)??10??C). Therefore, one electron volt is equal to 1.602176565(35)??10??J. Historically, the electron volt was devised as a standard unit of measure through its usefulness in electrostatic particle accelerator sciences because a particle with charge q has an energy E=qV after passing through the potential V; if q is quoted in integer units of the elementary charge and the terminal bias in volts, one gets an energy in eV.\nThe electron volt is not an SI unit and its value in SI units must be obtained experimentally. Like the elementary charge on which it is based, it is not an independent quantity but is equal to (1 J/C)(2 h ?? / ??0 c0) It is a common unit of energy within physics, widely used in solid state, atomic, nuclear, and particle physics. It is commonly used with the SI prefixes milli-, kilo-, mega-,</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Electronvolt</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.electronvolt_per_tesla">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">Enumeration for the unit Electronvolt per Tesla.</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">eV/T</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.electronvolt_second">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">Enumeration for the unit electronvolt second.</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Electronvolt Second</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.elementary_charge">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">The elementary charge, usually denoted as e, is the electric charge carried by a single proton, or equivalently, the negation (opposite) of the electric charge carried by a single electron. This elementary charge is a fundamental physical constant. To avoid confusion over its sign, e is sometimes called the elementary positive charge. This charge has a measured value of approximately 1.602176565(35)??10 coulombs. In the cgs system, e is 4.80320425(10)??10??statcoulombs.\nIn some natural unit systems, such as the system of atomic units, e functions as the unit of electric charge, that is e is equal to 1??e in those unit systems. The use of elementary charge as a unit was promoted by George Johnstone Stoney in 1874 for the first system of natural units, called Stoney units. Later, he proposed the name electron for this unit. At the time, the particle we now call the electron was not yet discovered and the difference between the particle electron and the unit of charge electron was still blurred. Later, the name electron was assigned to the particle and the unit of charge e lost its name. However, the unit of energy electronvolt reminds us that the elementary charge was once called</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Elementary charge</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.farad">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">The farad (symbol: F) is the SI derived unit of capacitance. The unit is named after the English physicist Michael Faraday.\nA farad is the charge in coulombs which a capacitor will accept for the potential across it to change 1 volt. A coulomb is 1 ampere second. Example: A capacitor with capacitance of 47 nF will increase by 1 volt per second with a 47 nA input current.\n1 microfarad (??F) = one millionth (10) of a farad, or 1000000 pF, or 1000 nF; 1 nanofarad (nF) = one billionth (10) of a farad, or 1000 pF; 1 picofarad (pF) = one trillionth (10) of a farad.\nA farad has the base SI representation of: s ?? A ?? m ?? kg\nIt can further be expressed as:\nA=ampere, V=volt, C=coulomb, J=joule, m=meter, N=newton, s=second, W=watt, kg=kilogram, ??=ohm\nFor electronics, one farad is a fairly large amount of capacitance. The most commonly used submultiples in electrical and electronic usage are the microfarad, nanofarad and picofarad.\nThe farad was coined by Josiah Latimer Clark in the year of 1861, in honor of Michael Faraday, but it was for a unit of quantity of charge.\nValues of capacitors are usually specified in ranges of farads (F), millifarads (mF), microfarads (??F), nanofarads (nF) or</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Farad</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.farad_per_metre">
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Farad per metre</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.foot-pound_force">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">The foot-pound force (symbol: ft??lbf or ft??lbf), or simply foot-pound (symbol: ft??lb) is a unit of work or energy in the Engineering and Gravitational Systems in United States customary and imperial units of measure. It is the energy transferred on applying a force of one pound-force (lbf) through a displacement of one foot. The corresponding SI unit is the joule.\nThe foot-pound is often used to specify the muzzle energy of a bullet in small arms ballistics, particularly in the United States.\n"Foot-pound" is sometimes also used as a unit of torque (see Pound-foot (torque)). In the United States this unit is often used to specify, for example, the tightness of a bolt or the output of an engine. Although they are dimensionally equivalent, energy (a scalar), and torque (a vector) are distinct physical quantities. Both energy and torque can be expressed as a product of a force vector with a displacement vector (hence pounds and feet); energy is the scalar product of the two, and torque is the vector product.\n1 foot-pound is equivalent to:</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Foot-pound force</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.g_force_measure">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">The g-force (with g from gravitational) associated with an object is its acceleration relative to free-fall. This acceleration experienced by an object is due to the vector sum of non-gravitational forces acting on an object free to move. The accelerations that are not produced by gravity are termed proper accelerations, and it is only these that are measured in g-force units. They cause stresses and strains on objects, which are felt as weight (any g-force can thus be simply described, and measured, as a "weight per unit mass"). Because of these strains (weight forces), large proper accelerations (large g-forces), may be destructive.\nGravitation acting alone does not produce a g-force, even though g-forces are expressed in multiples of the acceleration of a standard gravity. Thus, the standard gravitational acceleration at the Earth's surface produces g-force only indirectly, as a result of resistance to it by mechanical forces. The 1 g-force on an object sitting on the Earth's surface is caused by mechanical force exerted in the upward direction by the ground, keeping the object from going into free-fall. The upward force from the ground ensures that an object at rest on the</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">g-force</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.gallon">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">The gallon (abbreviation "gal"), with the US and imperial gallon, is a measure of volume. Historically it has had many definitions, but there are three definitions in current use: the imperial gallon (?????4.546??L) which since metrication is used colloquially in the United Kingdom and semi-officially within Canada, the United States (liquid) gallon (?????3.79??L), and the lesser used US dry gallon (?????4.40??L). The gallon, be it the imperial or US gallon, is sometimes found in other English-speaking countries.\nThere is one gallon defined in the imperial system but two (liquid and dry) in the US customary system.\nThe imperial (UK) gallon, defined as 4.54609??L, is used in some Commonwealth countries and was originally based on the volume of 10 pounds of water at 62????F (17????C). (A US liquid gallon of water weighs about 8.33 pounds at the same temperature.) The imperial fluid ounce is defined as ???160 of an imperial gallon.\nThis gallon is defined as 231 cubic inches, and is equal to exactly 3.785411784??litres or about 0.13368??cubic feet. This is the most common definition of a gallon in the United States. The US fluid ounce is defined as ???128 of a US liquid gallon.\nThis gallon is one-eighth of a</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Gallon (US)</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.gigaelectonvolt">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">Enumeration for the unit gigaelectonvolt</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Gigaelectonvolt</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.gigahertz_per_kelvin">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">Enumeration for the unit Gigahertz per Kelvin</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Gigahertz per Kelvin</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.gigawatt_hours">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">Enumeration representing the measurement unit of gigawatt-hours</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Gigawatt-hours</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.gram">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">The gram (alternative British English spelling: gramme; SI unit symbol: g) (Greek/Latin root gr??mma) is a metric system unit of mass.\nOriginally defined as "the absolute weight of a volume of pure water equal to the cube of the hundredth part of a metre, and at the temperature of melting ice" (later 4????C), a gram is now defined as one one-thousandth of the SI base unit, the kilogram, or 1??10 kg, which itself is defined as being equal to the mass of a physical prototype preserved by the International Bureau of Weights and Measures.\nThe International System of Units (SI) unit symbol for the gram is "g" following the numeric value with a space, as in "640??g". In some fields and regions, the SI symbols for units are used quite strictly, in particular in technical and scientific publications and in legally regulated product labels. In other contexts, a wide range of other abbreviations have been encountered, such as "gr", "gm", "grm", "gms" and "grms". The use of abbreviations such as "gm", "Gm", or "GM" for grams could potentially lead to serious errors in healthcare settings where accidentally transposing "gm" to "mg" (milligrams) would result in a 1000 times dosage difference. It</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Gram</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.gram_per_cubic_centimeter">
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Gram per cubic centimeter</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.grams_per_joule">
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Grams per joule</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.grams_per_kilonewton_second">
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Grams per kilonewton second</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.grams_per_kilowatt_hour">
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Grams per kilowatt-hour</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.grams_per_liter">
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Grams per Liter</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.grams_per_mole">
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Grams per mole</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.gray">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">The gray (symbol: Gy) is the SI derived unit of absorbed dose, specific energy (imparted) and of kerma. Such energies are typically associated with ionising radiation such as X-rays or gamma particles or with other nuclear particles. It is defined as the absorption of one joule of such energy by one kilogram of matter (usually human tissue).\nThe gray was named after the British physicist Louis Harold Gray, a pioneer in the field of measurement of radium radiation and X-rays and their effects on living tissue, and was adopted as part of SI by the 15th CGPM in 1975. The SI unit replaces the traditional cgs unit, the rad (equivalent to 0.01 Gy), which remains common in industry in the United States, while "strongly discouraged" in the style guide for U.S. National Institute of Standards and Technology authors.\nOne gray is the absorption of one joule of energy, in the form of ionizing radiation, per kilogram of matter.\nFor xrays and gamma rays, these are the same units as the sievert (Sv). For alpha particles one gray is twenty sievert. To avoid any risk of confusion between the absorbed dose (by matter) and the equivalent dose (by biological tissues), one must use the corresponding</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Gray</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.gray_per_second">
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Gray per second</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.hectoliter">
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Hectoliter</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.henry_measure">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">In physics, and electronics, the henry (symbol H) is the SI derived unit of inductance. It is named after Joseph Henry (1797???1878), the American scientist who discovered electromagnetic induction independently of and at about the same time as Michael Faraday (1791???1867) in England. The magnetic permeability of the vacuum is 4????10 H/m (henry per meter).\nThe National Institute of Standards and Technology provides guidance for American users of SI to write the plural as henries.\nIf the rate of change of current in a circuit is one ampere per second and the resulting electromotive force is one volt, then the inductance of the circuit is one henry. Other equivalent combinations of SI units are as follows:\nwhere\nA = ampere\nC = coulomb\nF = farad\nJ = joule\nkg = kilogram\nm = meter\ns = second\nWb = weber\nV = volt\n?? = ohm.</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Henry</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.henry_per_metre">
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Henry per metre</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.hertz">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">The hertz (symbol Hz) is the SI unit of frequency defined as the number of cycles per second of a periodic phenomenon. One of its most common uses is the description of the sine wave, particularly those used in radio and audio applications, such as the frequency of musical tones. The word "hertz" is named for Heinrich Rudolf Hertz, who was the first to conclusively prove the existence of electromagnetic waves.\nThe hertz is equivalent to cycles per second. In defining the second, the CIPM declared that "the standard to be employed is the transition between the hyperfine levels F??=??4, M??= ??0 and F??=??3, M??=??0 of the ground state 2S1/2 of the cesium 133 atom, unperturbed by external fields, and that the frequency of this transition is assigned the value 9??192??631??770 hertz" thereby effectively defining the hertz and the second simultaneously.\nIn English, "hertz" is also used as the plural form. As an SI unit, Hz can be prefixed; commonly used multiples are kHz (kilohertz, 10??Hz), MHz (megahertz, 10??Hz), GHz (gigahertz, 10??Hz) and THz (terahertz, 10??Hz). One hertz simply means "one cycle per second" (typically that which is being counted is a complete cycle); 100??Hz means "one hundred</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Hertz</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.hertz_per_kelvin">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">Enumeration for the unit Hertz per Kelvin.</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Hertz per Kelvin</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.hertz_per_tesla">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">Enumeration for the unit Hertz per Tesla.</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Hertz per Tesla</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.hertz_per_volt">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">Enumeration for the unit Hertz per Volt.</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Hertz per Volt</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.horsepower">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">Horsepower (hp) is the name of several units of measurement of power, the rate at which work is done. The most common conversion factor, especially for electrical power, is 1 hp = 746 watts. The term was adopted in the late 18th century by Scottish engineer James Watt to compare the output of steam engines with the power of draft horses. It was later expanded to include the output power of other types of piston engines, as well as turbines, electric motors and other machinery. The definition of the unit varied between geographical regions. Most countries now use the SI unit watt for measurement of power. With the implementation of the EU Directive 80/181/EEC on January 1, 2010, the use of horsepower in the EU is only permitted as supplementary unit.\nUnits called "horsepower" have differing definitions:\nThe development of the steam engine provided a reason to compare the output of horses with that of the engines that could replace them. In 1702, Thomas Savery wrote in The Miner's Friend: "So that an engine which will raise as much water as two horses, working together at one time in such a work, can do, and for which there must be constantly kept ten or twelve horses for doing the</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Horsepower</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.hour">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">The hour (common symbol: h or hr) is a unit of measurement of time. In modern usage, an hour comprises 60 minutes, or 3,600 seconds. It is approximately 1/24 of a mean solar day.\nAn hour in the Universal Coordinated Time (UTC) time standard can include a negative or positive leap second, and may therefore have a duration of 3,599 or 3,601 seconds for adjustment purposes.\nAlthough it is not a standard defined by the International System of Units, the hour is a unit accepted for use with SI, represented by the symbol h.\nThe Middle English word ure first appears in the 13th century, as a loanword from Old French ure, ore, from Latin hora. Hora, in turn, derives from Greek ??????? ("season, time of day, hour"). In terms of the Proto-Indo-European language, ??????? is a cognate of English year and is derived from the Proto-Indo-European word *i????ro- ("year, summer").\nThe ure of Middle English and the Anglo-French houre gradually supplanted the Old English nouns t??d (which survives in Modern English as tide) and stund. Stund is the progenitor of stound, which remains an archaic synonym for hour. Stund is related to the Old High German stunta, from Germanic *stund?? ("time, interval,</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Hour</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.hours_per_week">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">An enumeration value representing the unit of hours per week, e.g. in the context of hours worked.</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Hour</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.inch">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">An inch (plural: inches; abbreviation or symbol: in or ??? ??? a double prime) is the name of a unit of length in a number of different systems, including Imperial units, and United States customary units. There are 36??inches in a yard and 12??inches in a foot. Corresponding units of area and volume are the square inch and the cubic inch.\nThe inch is a commonly used customary unit of length in the United States, Canada, and the United Kingdom. For the United Kingdom, guidance on public sector use states that since 1 October 1995, without time limit, that the inch (along with the mile, yard and foot) is to be used as a primary unit for road signs and related measurements of distance and speed and may continue to be used as a secondary or supplementary indication following a metric measurement for other purposes.\nFrom July 1, 1959, the United States and countries of the British Commonwealth defined the length of the international yard to be exactly 0.9144 metres. Consequently, the international inch is defined as exactly 25.4 millimetres. This creates a slight difference between the international units and American surveyor's units which are described in the article on the foot.\nThe</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Inch</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.international_unit">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">In pharmacology, the International Unit is a unit of measurement for the amount of a substance, based on biological activity or effect. It is abbreviated as IU, as UI (Spanish unidad internacional or French unit?? internationale or Italian unit?? internazionale), or as IE (German Internationale Einheit, Danish International Enhed, Swedish Internationell Enhet). It is used to quantify vitamins, hormones, some medications, vaccines, blood products, and similar biologically active substances.\nMany biological agents exist in different forms or preparations (e.g. vitamin A in the form of retinol or beta-carotene). The goal of the IU is to be able to compare these, so that different forms or preparations with the same biological effect will contain the same number of IUs. To do so, the WHO Expert Committee on Biological Standardization provides a reference preparation of the agent, arbitrarily sets the number of IUs contained in that preparation, and specifies a biological procedure to compare other preparations of the same agent to the reference preparation. Since the number of IUs contained in a new substance is arbitrarily set, there is no equivalence between IU measurements of</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">International unit</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.inverse_kelvin">
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Inverse Kelvin</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.inverse_meter">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">Enumeration for the unit Inverse Meter.</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">m^-1</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.joule">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">The joule (??/??d??u??l/ or sometimes /??d??a??l/); symbol J) is a derived unit of energy, work, or amount of heat in the International System of Units. It is equal to the energy expended (or work done) in applying a force of one newton through a distance of one meter (1 newton metre or N??m), or in passing an electric current of one ampere through a resistance of one ohm for one second. It is named after the English physicist James Prescott Joule (1818???1889).\nIn terms firstly of base SI units and then in terms of other SI units:\nwhere N is the newton, m is the meter, kg is the kilogram, s is the second, Pa is the pascal, and W is the watt.\nOne joule can also be defined as:\nThis SI unit is named after James Prescott Joule. As with every International System of Units (SI) unit whose name is derived from the proper name of a person, the first letter of its symbol is upper case (J). When an SI unit is spelled out in English, it should always begin with a lower case letter (joule), except where any word would be capitalized, such as at the beginning of a sentence or in capitalized material such as a title. Note that "degree Celsius" conforms to this rule because the "d" is lowercase. ???Based on</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Joule</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.joule_meter">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">Enumeration for the unit Joule Meter.</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Joule Meter</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.joule_meter_per_mole">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">Enumeration for the unit Joule Meter per Mole.</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">J m/mol</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.joule_per_cubic_metre">
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Joule per cubic metre</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.joule_per_cubic_metre_per_kelvin">
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Joule per cubic metre per kelvin</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.joule_per_kelvin">
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Joule per kelvin</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.joule_per_kilogram">
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Joule per kilogram</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.joule_per_kilogram_per_kelvin">
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Joule per kilogram per kelvin</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.joule_per_mole">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">The joule per mole (symbol: J??mol) is an SI derived unit of energy per amount of material. Energy is measured in joules, and the amount of material is measured in moles.\nPhysical quantities measured in J??mol usually describe quantities of energy transferred during phase transformations or chemical reactions. Division by the number of moles facilitates comparison between processes involving different quantities of material and between similar processes involving different types of materials. The meaning of such a quantity is always context-dependent and, particularly for chemical reactions, is dependent on the (possibly arbitrary) definition of a 'mole' for a particular process.\nFor convenience and due to the range of magnitudes involved, these quantities are almost always reported in kJ??mol rather than in J??mol. For example, heats of fusion and vaporization are usually of the order of 10??kJ??mol, bond energies are of the order of 100??kJ??mol, and ionization energies of the order of 1000??kJ??mol.\n1??kJ??mol is equal to 0.239??kcal??mol or 1.04??10??eV per particle. At room temperature (25????C, 77????F, or 298.15??K) 1??kJ??mol is equal to 0.4034??kBT.</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Joule per mole</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.joule_per_mole_per_kelvin">
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Joule per mole per kelvin</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.joule_per_tesla">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">Enumeration for the unit Joule per Tesla.</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Joule per Tesla</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.joule_per_tesla_squared">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">Enumeration for the unit Joule per Tesla squared.</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">JT^-2</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.joule_second">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">Enumeration for the unit Joule Second.</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Joule Second</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.joule_second_per_mole">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">Enumeration for the unit J s/mol.</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">J s/mol</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.julian_year">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">In astronomy, a Julian year (symbol: a) is a unit of measurement of time defined as exactly 365.25 days of 86,400 SI seconds each. The Julian year is the average length of the year in the Julian calendar used in Western societies in previous centuries, and for which the unit is named. Nevertheless, because an astronomical Julian year measures duration rather than designating a date, this Julian year does not correspond to years in the Julian calendar or any other calendar. Nor does it correspond to the many other ways of defining a year.\nThe Julian year is not a fundamental unit of measurement in the International System of Units (SI), but it is recognized by the International Astronomical Union (IAU) as a non-SI unit for use in astronomy. Before 1984, both the Julian year and the mean tropical year were used by astronomers. In 1898, Simon Newcomb used both in his Tables of the Sun in the form of the Julian century (36,525??days) and the "solar century" (36,524.22??days), a rounded form of 100 mean tropical years of 365.24219879??days each according to Newcomb. However, the mean tropical year is not suitable as a unit of measurement because it varies from year to year by a small</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Julian year</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.katal">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">The katal (symbol: kat) is the SI unit of catalytic activity. It is a derived SI unit for expressing quantity values of catalytic activity of enzymes and other catalysts. Its use is recommended by the General Conference on Weights and Measures and other international organizations. It replaces the non-SI enzyme unit. Enzyme units are, however, still more commonly used than the katal in practice at present, especially in biochemistry.\nThe katal is not used to express the rate of a reaction; that is expressed in units of concentration per second (or moles per liter per second). Rather, it is used to express catalytic activity which is a property of the catalyst. The katal is invariant of the measurement procedure, but the numerical quantity value is not and depends on the experimental conditions. Therefore, in order to define the quantity of a catalyst, the rate of conversion of a defined chemical reaction has to be specified, preferably of the first order, under strictly controlled conditions. One katal of trypsin, for example, is that amount of trypsin which breaks a mole of peptide bonds per second under specified conditions.\nThe name katal has been used for decades and it became</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Katal</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.katal_per_cubic_metre">
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Katal per cubic metre</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.kelvin">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">The kelvin is a unit of measurement for temperature. It is one of the seven base units in the International System of Units (SI) and is assigned the unit symbol K. The Kelvin scale is an absolute, thermodynamic temperature scale using as its null point absolute zero, the temperature at which all thermal motion ceases in the classical description of thermodynamics. The kelvin is defined as the fraction ???273.16 of the thermodynamic temperature of the triple point of water (273.16 K (0.01????C; 32.02????F)).\nThe Kelvin scale is named after the Belfast-born, Glasgow University engineer and physicist William Thomson, 1st Baron Kelvin (1824???1907), who wrote of the need for an "absolute thermometric scale". Unlike the degree Fahrenheit and degree Celsius, the kelvin is not referred to or typeset as a degree. The kelvin is the primary unit of measurement in the physical sciences, but is often used in conjunction with the degree Celsius, which has the same magnitude. Subtracting 273.16??K from the temperature of the triple point of water (0.01????C) makes absolute zero (0??K) equivalent to ???273.15 ??C (???459.67????F).\nWhen reference is made to the unit kelvin (either a specific temperature or a</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Kelvin</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.kelvin_per_tesla">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">Enumeration for the unit Kelvin per Tesla.</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Kelvin per Tesla</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.kilobit">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">The kilobit is a multiple of the unit bit for digital information or computer storage. The prefix kilo (symbol k) is defined in the International System of Units (SI) as a multiplier of 10 (1 thousand), and therefore,\nThe kilobit has the unit symbol kbit or kb.\nUsing the common byte size of 8 bits, 1 kbit is equal to 125 bytes.\nThe kilobit is closely related to the kibibit, a unit multiple derived from the binary prefix kibi (symbol Ki) of the same order of magnitude, which is equal to 2bits = 1024bits, or approximately 2% larger than the kilobit. Despite the definitions of these new prefixes for binary-based quantities of storage by international standards organizations, memory semiconductor chips are still marketed using the metric prefix names to designate binary multiples.\nThe kilobit is most commonly used in the expression of data rates of digital communication circuits as kilobits per second (kbit/s or kb/s), or abbreviated as kbps, as in, for example, a 56 kbps PSTN circuit, or a 512 kbit/s broadband Internet connection.\nThe unit symbol kb is typographically similar to unit symbols of the kilobyte, i.e. kB, with an upper case B. The International Electrotechnical Commission</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Kilobit</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.kilobyte">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">A unit of measure equal to 1,000 bytes.</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Kilobyte</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.kilogram">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">The kilogram or kilogramme (SI symbol: kg), also known as the kilo, is the base unit of mass in the International System of Units and is defined as being equal to the mass of the International Prototype Kilogram (IPK), which is almost exactly equal to the mass of one liter of water. The avoirdupois (or international) pound, used in both the Imperial system and U.S. customary units, is defined as exactly 0.45359237??kg, making one kilogram approximately equal to 2.2046 avoirdupois pounds.\nIn everyday usage, the mass of an object given in kilograms is often referred to as its weight, which is the measure of the gravitational force???or heaviness???of an object. Weight given in kilograms is technically the non???SI unit of measure known as the kilogram-force. The equivalent unit of force in the avoirdupois system of measurement is the pound-force. In strict scientific contexts, forces are typically measured with the SI unit newton.\nThe kilogram is the only SI base unit with an SI prefix as part of its name. It is also the only SI unit that is still directly defined by an artifact rather than a fundamental physical property that can be reproduced in different laboratories. Four of the seven</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Kilogram</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.kilogram_meter_per_second">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">Enumeration for the unit Kilogram meter per second.</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Kg m/s</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.kilogram_oil_equivalents">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">Enumeration representing the measurement unit of Kilogram of oik equivalents</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Kilogram of Oil Equivalents</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.kilogram_per_cubic_metre">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">Kilogram per cubic metre is an SI derived unit of density, defined by mass in kilograms divided by volume in cubic metres. The official SI symbolic abbreviation is kg??m, or equivalently either kg/m or .\n1??kg??m is equivalent to:\n1 g??cm = 1000??kg??m = 1,000,000 g??m (exactly)\n1 lb??ft ??? 16.02??kg??m (approximately)\n1 oz??gal ??? 7.489??kg??m (approximately)\nThe kilogram was originally based on the mass of one litre of water, thus the density of water is about 1000??kg??m. In the Chemistry field, g??cm is more commonly used.</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Kilogram per cubic metre</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.kilogram_per_mole">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">Enumeration for the unit Kilogram per Mole.</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Kg/mol</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.kilogram_per_square_metre">
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Kilogram per square metre</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.kilohertz_measure">
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Kilohertz</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.kilojoule">
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Kilojoule</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.kilojoule_per_mole">
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Kilojoule per mole</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.kilometer">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">The kilometre (American spelling: kilometer; SI symbol: km) is a unit of length in the metric system, equal to one thousand metres (kilo- being the SI prefix for 1000). It is now the measurement unit used officially for expressing distances between geographical places on land in most of the world; notable exceptions are the United States and the United Kingdom where the statute mile is the official unit used.\nk (pronounced kay) is occasionally used in some English-speaking countries as an alternative for the word kilometre in everyday writing and speech. A slang term for the kilometre in the U.S. military is klick.\nThere are two common pronunciations for the word:\nThe former pronunciation follows the general pattern in English whereby SI units of measurement are pronounced with the stress on the first syllable, and the pronunciation of the actual base unit does not change irresepective of the prefix. It is generally preferred by the British Broadcasting Corporation (BBC) and the Australian Broadcasting Corporation (ABC).\nMany scientists and other users, particularly in countries where the Metric System (SI) is not widely used, use the pronunciation with stress on the second</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Kilometer</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.kilometer_per_second_per_megaparsec">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">Enumeration for the unit Kilometer per Second per Megaparsec.</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Km/s/Mpc</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.kilometre_per_litre">
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Kilometre per litre</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.kilometres_per_hour">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">The kilometre per hour (American English: kilometer per hour) is a unit of speed, expressing the number of kilometres travelled in one hour. The unit symbol is km/h or km??h.\nWorldwide, the km/h is the most commonly used speed unit on road signs and car speedometers. Along with the kilowatt hour, km/h is the most commonly used metric unit based on the hour, although the "hour", while not an SI unit, is accepted for use with the International System of Units by the International Bureau of Weights and Measures (BIPM).\nIn Australian and North American slang and military usage, km/h is commonly pronounced, and sometimes even written, as klicks or kays (K's), although these may also be used to refer to kilometres.\nThe colloquial abbreviations "kph" and "kmph" are sometimes also used in some English-speaking countries, in analogy to "miles per hour" (mph), even though the official recommendation from the BIPM is to use "km/h". The symbol (as opposed to abbreviation) is in near-universal use elsewhere, even though the letters "km" and "h" do not always correspond to "kilometres" or "hours" in the language concerned.\nThe following are translations of the text "kilometres per hour" where</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Kilometres per hour</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.kilometres_per_second">
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Kilometres per second</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.kilonewton">
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">KiloNewton</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.kilopascal">
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Kilopascal</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.kilotonne_of_oil_equivalent">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">Enumeration representing unit kilotonne of oil equivalent.</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Kt of Oil Equivalent</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.kilowatt_measure">
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Kilowatt</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.knot_measure">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">The knot (pronounced not) is a unit of speed equal to one nautical mile (1.852??km) per hour, approximately 1.151??mph. The abbreviation kn is preferred by the International Hydrographic Organization (IHO), which includes every major seafaring nation; but the abbreviations kt (singular) and kts (plural) are also widely used  conflicting with the SI symbol for kilotonne which is also "kt". The knot is a non-SI unit accepted for use with the International System of Units (SI). Worldwide, the knot is used in meteorology, and in maritime and air navigation???for example, a vessel travelling at 1 knot along a meridian travels one minute of geographic latitude in one hour. Etymologically, the term knot derives from counting the number of knots in the line that unspooled from the reel of a chip log in a specific time.\n1,852??m is the length of the internationally agreed nautical mile. The US adopted the international definition in 1954, having previously used the US nautical mile (1,853.248??m). The UK adopted the international nautical mile definition in 1970, having previously used the UK Admiralty nautical mile (6,080??ft [1,853.184??m]).\n(Values in bold face are exact.)\nThe speeds of vessels</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Knot</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.liter">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">The litre (American spelling: liter; SI symbol l or L) is a non-SI metric system unit of volume equal to 1 cubic decimetre (dm), 1,000 cubic centimetres (cm) or 1/1,000 cubic metre. If the lower case L is used as the symbol, it is sometimes rendered as a cursive ??? to help distinguish it from the capital "I", although this usage has no official approval by any international bureau.\nThe word litre is derived from an older French unit, the litron, whose name came from Greek via Latin. The original French metric system used the litre as a base unit, and it has been used in several subsequent versions of the metric system and is accepted for use with the SI, although not an official SI unit????? the SI unit of volume is the cubic metre (m). The spelling of the word used by the International Bureau of Weights and Measures is "litre" and this is also the usual one in most English-speaking countries, but in American English the spelling is "liter", being endorsed by the United States.\nOne litre of liquid water has a mass of almost exactly one kilogram, due to the gram being defined in 1795 as one cubic centimetre of water at the temperature of melting ice.\nA litre is defined as a special name</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Liter</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.litre_per_kilometre">
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Litre per kilometre</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.lumen_measure">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">The lumen (symbol: lm) is the SI derived unit of luminous flux, a measure of the total "amount" of visible light emitted by a source. Luminous flux differs from power (radiant flux) in that luminous flux measurements reflect the varying sensitivity of the human eye to different wavelengths of light, while radiant flux measurements indicate the total power of all light emitted, independent of the eye's ability to perceive it.\nThe lumen is defined in relation to the candela as\nA full sphere has a solid angle of 4???? steradians, so a light source that uniformly radiates one candela in all directions has a total luminous flux of 1??cd??4????sr??=??4?????????12.57??lumens.\nIf a light source emits one candela of luminous intensity uniformly across a solid angle of one steradian, the total luminous flux emitted into that angle is one lumen (1 cd??1 sr = 1??lm). Alternatively, an isotropic one-candela light-source emits a total luminous flux of exactly 4?? lumens. If the source were partially covered by an ideal absorbing hemisphere, that system would radiate half as much luminous flux???only 2?? lumens. The luminous intensity would still be one candela in those directions that are not obscured.\nThe lumen</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Lumen</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.lux">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">The lux (symbol: lx) is the SI unit of illuminance and luminous emittance, measuring luminous flux per unit area. It is used in photometry as a measure of the intensity, as perceived by the human eye, of light that hits or passes through a surface. It is analogous to the radiometric unit watts per square metre, but with the power at each wavelength weighted according to the luminosity function, a standardized model of human visual brightness perception. In English, "lux" is used in both singular and plural.\nIlluminance is a measure of how much luminous flux is spread over a given area. One can think of luminous flux (measured in lumens) as a measure of the total "amount" of visible light present, and the illuminance as a measure of the intensity of illumination on a surface. A given amount of light will illuminate a surface more dimly if it is spread over a larger area, so illuminance is inversely proportional to area.\nOne lux is equal to one lumen per square metre:\nA flux of 1,000 lumens, concentrated into an area of one square metre, lights up that square metre with an illuminance of 1,000 lux. However, the same 1,000 lumens, spread out over ten square metres, produces a dimmer</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Lux</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.measurement_system">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">Property relating an mso:type.unit to the mso:measurement_unit.measurement_system that uses this unit.</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Measurement System</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.property" />
    <mso:type.property.expected_type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/measurement_unit.measurement_system" />
    <mso:type.property.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.megabyte">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">A unit of measure equal to 1,000,000 bytes.</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Megabyte</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.megaelectronvolt">
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Megaelectronvolt</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.megahertz">
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Megahertz</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.megahertz_per_tesla">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">Enumeration for the unit Megahertz per Tesla.</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">MHz/T</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.megapascal">
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Megapascal</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.megapixel">
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Megapixel</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.meter">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">The metre (meter in the US), symbol m, is the base unit of length in the International System of Units (SI). Originally intended to be one ten-millionth of the distance from the Earth's equator to the North Pole (at sea level), its definition has been periodically refined to reflect growing knowledge of metrology. Since 1983, it has been defined as "the length of the path travelled by light in vacuum during a time interval of ???299,792,458 of a second".\nThe first recorded proposal for a decimal-based unit of length was the universal measure unit proposed by the English philosopher John Wilkins in 1668. In 1675, the Italian scientist Tito Livio Burattini, in his work Misura Universale, used the words metro cattolico (lit. "catholic [i.e. universal] metre"), which was derived from the Greek ???????????? ?????????????????? (m??tron katholik??n), "a universal measure". This word gave rise to the French m??tre which in 1797 was introduced into the English language.\nIn 1668, Wilkins proposed using Christopher Wren's suggestion of a pendulum with a half-period of one second to measure a standard length that Christiaan Huygens had observed to be 38 Rhineland or 39???4 English inches (997??mm) in length. In the</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Meter</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.meter_kelvin">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">Enumeration for the unit Meter Kelvin.</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Meter Kelvin</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.meters_per_square_second">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">An enumeration value expressing the unit of meters per square second.</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Meters per Square Second</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.metre_per_second">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">Metre per second (U.S. spelling: meter per second) is an SI derived unit of both speed (scalar) and velocity (vector quantity which specifies both magnitude and a specific direction), defined by distance in metres divided by time in seconds.\nThe official SI symbolic abbreviation is m??s, or equivalently either m/s or . Where metres per second are several orders of magnitude too slow to be convenient, such as in astronomical measurements, velocities may be given in kilometres per second, where 1??km/s is 1000 metres per second.\n1??m/s is equivalent to:\n1??foot??per??second = 0.3048??m??s (exactly)\n1??mile??per??hour??=??0.44704??m??s (exactly)\n1??km??h????? 0.2778??m??s (approximately)\n1 kilometre per second is equivalent to:\nAlthough m??s is an SI derived unit, it could be viewed as more fundamental than the metre, since the metre is now derived from the speed of light in a vacuum, which is defined as exactly 299??792??458??m??s by the BIPM. One metre per second is 1/299??792??458 of the speed of light in a vacuum.</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Metre per second</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.metre_per_second_squared">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">The metre (or meter) per second squared is the unit of acceleration in the International System of Units (SI). As a derived unit it is composed from the SI base units of length, the metre, and the standard unit of time, the second. Its symbol is written in several forms as m/s, m??s, or m??s.\nAs acceleration, the unit is interpreted physically as change in velocity or speed per time interval, i.e. metre per second per second.\nAn object experiences a constant acceleration of one metre per second squared (1 m/s) from a state of rest, when it achieves the speed of 5 m/s after 5 seconds and 10 m/s after 10 seconds.\nNewton's Second Law states that force equals mass multiplied by acceleration. The unit of force is the newton (N), and mass has the SI unit kilogram (kg). One newton equals one kilogram metre per second squared. Therefore, the unit metre per second squared is equivalent to newton per kilogram, N??kg, or N/kg.\nThus, the Earth's gravitational field (near ground level) can be quoted as 9.8 metres per second squared, or the equivalent 9.8 N/kg.\nAcceleration can be measured in ratios to gravity, such as g-force, and peak ground acceleration in earthquakes.</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Metre per second squared</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.mev_c">
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">MeV/c??</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.microgram">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">The microgram (SI unit symbol: ??g) is a metric system unit of mass.</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">microgram</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.mile">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">A mile is a unit of length, most commonly 5,280 feet (1,760 yards, or about 1,609 metres). The mile of 5,280 feet is sometimes called the statute mile or land mile to distinguish it from the nautical mile (1,852 metres, about 6,076.1 feet). There have also been many historical miles and similar units in other systems that may be translated into English as miles; they have varied in length from 1 to 15 kilometres.\nThe exact length of the land mile varied slightly among English-speaking countries until an international agreement in 1959 established the yard as exactly 0.9144 metres, giving a mile of exactly 1,609.344 metres. The United States adopted this international mile for most purposes, but retained the pre-1959 mile for some land-survey data, terming it the US survey mile. In the US, statute mile formally refers to the survey mile, about 3.219??mm (?????inch) longer than the international mile (the international mile is exactly 0.0002% less than the US survey mile).\nUse of the mile as a unit of measurement is now largely confined to the United Kingdom, the United States, and, rarely, Canada.\nThe word mile originally derives from the Old English word m??l which in turn was</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Mile</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.mile_per_gallon">
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Mile per gallon</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.milliampere_hour">
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Milliampere-hour</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.millibar">
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Millibar</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.milligram">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">The milligram (SI unit symbol: mg) is a metric system unit of mass.</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">milligram</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.milligram_per_deciliter">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">A measure of the concentration of a given substance in a given liquid.  It is often used to measure the concentration of substances in the blood, e.g. cholesterol or blood sugar. </mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Milligram per Deciliter</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.milliliter">
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Milliliter</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.millimeter">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">The millimetre (American spelling: millimeter; SI unit symbol mm; informal abbreviation: mil) is a unit of length in the metric system, equal to one thousandth of a metre, which is the SI base unit of length.\nIt is equal to 1,000 micrometres and 1,000,000 nanometres. There are 25.4 mm in one inch.\nFor the purposes of compatibility with Chinese, Japanese and Korean (CJK) characters, Unicode has symbols for:\nThey are useful for East Asian fixed-width CJK typography, because they are equal in proportion to one Chinese character.</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Millimeter</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.millimeter_of_mercury">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">A measure of pressure, specifically the extra pressure exerted by a column of mercury one millimeter high. </mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Millimeter of Mercury</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.millimeter_per_kelvin">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">Enumeration for the unit Millimeter per Kelvin.</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Millimeter per Kelvin</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.millimole_per_liter">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">A measure of molar concentration.  The number of thousandths of moles in a liter of the given substance. </mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Millimole per Liter</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.million_years">
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Million years</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.millisecond">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">A thousandth of a second.</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Millisecond</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.minute">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">A minute is a unit of measurement of time or of angle. The minute is a unit of time equal to 1/60 (the first sexagesimal fraction) of an hour or 60 seconds.</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Minute</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.minute_of_arc">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">A minute of arc, arcminute, or minute arc (MOA), is a unit of angular measurement equal to one sixtieth (???60) of one degree (???21,600), or (???10,800) radians. In turn, a second of arc or arcsecond is one sixtieth (???60) of one minute of arc. Since one degree is defined as one three hundred and sixtieth (???360) of a rotation, one minute of arc is ???21,600 of a rotation. It is used in those fields which require a unit for the expression of small angles, such as astronomy, navigation and marksmanship.\nThe number of square arcminutes in a complete sphere is\nor approximately 148,510,660.498 square arcminutes.\nThe arcsecond is ???3,600 of a degree, or ???1,296,000 of a circle, or (???648,000) radians, which is approximately ???206,265 radian.\nTo express even smaller angles, standard SI prefixes can be employed; in particular, the milliarcsecond, abbreviated mas, is used in astronomy.\nThe standard symbol for marking the arcminute is the prime (???) (U+2032), though a single quote (') (U+0027) is commonly used where only ASCII characters are permitted. One arcminute is thus written 1???. It is also abbreviated as arcmin or amin or, less commonly, the prime with a circumflex over it ().\nThe standard symbol</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Minute of arc</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.mole_measure">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">The mole is a unit of measurement used in chemistry to express amounts of a chemical substance, defined as an amount of a substance that contains as many elementary entities (e.g., atoms, molecules, ions, electrons) as there are atoms in 12 grams of pure carbon-12 (C), the isotope of carbon with atomic weight 12. This corresponds to a value of 6.02214179(30)??10 elementary entities of the substance. It is one of the base units in the International System of Units, and has the unit symbol mol.\nThe mole is widely used in chemistry, instead of units of mass or volume, as a convenient way to express the amounts of reactants and products of chemical reactions. For example, the chemical equation 2 H2 + O2 ??? 2 H2O implies that 2??mol of dihydrogen and 1??mol of dioxygen react to form 2??mol of water. The mole may also be used to express the number of atoms, ions, or other elementary entities in some sample. The concentration of a solution is commonly expressed by its molarity, the number of moles of the dissolved substance per litre of solution.\nThe number of molecules in a mole (known as Avogadro's number) is defined so that the mass of one mole of a substance, expressed in grams, is exactly</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Mole</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.mole_per_cubic_metre">
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Mole per cubic metre</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.month">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">One of the twelve named periods into which a year is divided.</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Month</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.nautical_mile">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">The nautical mile (symbol M, NM or nmi) is a unit of length that is about one minute of arc of latitude measured along any meridian, or about one minute of arc of longitude at the equator. By international agreement it is exactly 1,852 metres (approximately 6,076 feet).\nIt is a non-SI unit (although accepted for use in the International System of Units by the BIPM) used especially by navigators in the shipping and aviation industries, and also in polar exploration. It is commonly used in international law and treaties, especially regarding the limits of territorial waters. It developed from the sea mile and the related geographical mile.\nThe nautical mile remains in use by sea and air navigators worldwide because of its convenience when working with charts. Most nautical charts are constructed on the Mercator projection whose scale varies by approximately a factor of six from the equator to 80?? north or south latitude. It is, therefore, impossible to show a single linear scale for use on charts on scales smaller than about 1/80,000. The nautical mile circumvents this problem by being equal to a minute of latitude on a chart, which allows any distance measured with a chart divider</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Nautical mile</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.newton">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">The newton (symbol: N) is the SI derived unit of force. It is named after Isaac Newton in recognition of his work on classical mechanics, specifically Newton's second law of motion.\nThe newton is the SI unit for force; it is equal to the amount of net force required to accelerate a mass of one kilogram at a rate of one metre per second squared. Newton's second law of motion states: F = ma, multiplying m (kg) by a (m/s), The newton is therefore:\nUnits used:\nIn dimensional analysis:\nwhere\nKilonewtons are often used for stating safety holding values of fasteners, anchors, and more in the building industry. They are also often used in the specifications for rock climbing equipment. The safe working loads in both tension and shear measurements can be stated in kilonewtons. Injection moulding machines, used to manufacture plastic parts, are classed by kilonewton (i.e., the amount of clamping force they apply to the mould).\nOn the Earth's surface, 1??kN is about 101.97162 kilogram-force of load, but multiplying the kilonewton value by 100 (i.e. using a slightly conservative and easier to calculate value) is a good rule of thumb.</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Newton</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.newton_meter_squared_per_kilogram_squared">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">Enumeration for the unit Newton Meter Squared per Kilogram Squared.</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Nm^2/kg^2</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.newton_metre">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">A newton metre is a unit of torque (also called "moment") in the SI system. The symbolic form is Nm or N??m, and sometimes hyphenated newton-metre. One newton metre is equal to the torque resulting from a force of one newton applied perpendicularly to a moment arm which is one metre long.\nIt is also used less commonly as a unit of work, or energy, in which case it is equivalent to the more common and standard SI unit of energy, the joule. In this very different usage the metre term represents the distance travelled or displacement in the direction of the force, and not the perpendicular distance from a fulcrum as it does when used to express torque. This usage is discouraged by the SI authority, since it can lead to confusion as to whether a given quantity expressed in newton metres is a torque or a quantity of energy.</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Newton metre</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.newton_per_ampere_squared">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">Enumeration for the unit Newton per Ampere Squared.</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">N/A^2</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.newton_per_metre">
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Newton per metre</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.night">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">Enumeration representing the units of nights. Hotel stays and travels are often measured this way.</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Night</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.nuclear_magneton">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">The nuclear magneton (symbol ??N), is a physical constant of magnetic moment, defined by:\nwhere:\nIn SI units, its value is approximately:\nThe nuclear magneton is the natural unit for expressing magnetic dipole moments of heavy particles such as nucleons and atomic nuclei. On the contrary, the dipole moment of the electron, which is much higher as a consequence of much higher charge-to-mass ratio, is usually expressed in corresponding units of the Bohr magneton.</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Nuclear magneton</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.ohm">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">The ohm (symbol: ??) is the SI derived unit of electrical resistance, named after German physicist Georg Simon Ohm.\nThe ohm is defined as a resistance between two points of a conductor when a constant potential difference of 1 volt, applied to these points, produces in the conductor a current of 1 ampere, the conductor not being the seat of any electromotive force.\nwhere:\nIn many cases the resistance of a conductor in ohms is approximately constant within a certain range of voltages, temperatures, and other parameters; one speaks of linear resistors. In other cases resistance varies (e.g., thermistors).\nCommonly used multiples and submultiples in electrical and electronic usage are the milliohm, ohm, kilohm, megohm, and gigaohm.\nIn alternating current circuits, electrical impedance is also measured in ohms.\nThe siemens (symbol: S) is the SI derived unit of electric conductance and admittance, also known as the mho (ohm spelled backwards, symbol is ???); it is the reciprocal of resistance in ohms.\nThe power dissipated by a linear resistor may be calculated from its resistance, and voltage or current. The formula is a combination of Ohm's law and Joule's laws:\nwhere P is the power in</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Ohm</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.ohm_meter">
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Ohm meter</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.ounce_volume">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">A unit of volume or capacity equal to 1/16th of an American pint and 1/20th of an Imperial/British pint.</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Ounce - Volume</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.ounce_weight">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">A unit of weight equal to 1/16th of a pound avoirdupois.</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Ounce - Weight</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.parsec">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">The parsec (symbol: pc) is a unit of length used in astronomy. It is about 3.26??light-years, which is about 30.9??trillion??(3.09??10)??kilometres or about 19.2 trillion (1.92??10) miles.\nThe name parsec is "an abbreviated form of 'a distance corresponding to a parallax of one second'." It was coined in 1913 at the suggestion of British astronomer Herbert Hall Turner. A parsec is the distance from the Sun to an astronomical object which has a parallax angle of one arcsecond.\nThe parsec is equal to the length of the adjacent side of an imaginary right triangle in space. The two dimensions on which this triangle is based are the angle (which is defined as 1 arcsecond), and the opposite side (which is defined as 1 astronomical unit, which is the distance from the Earth to the Sun). Using these two measurements, along with the rules of trigonometry, the length of the adjacent side (the parsec) can be found.\nOne of the oldest methods for astronomers to calculate the distance to a star was to record the difference in angle between two measurements of the position of the star in the sky. The first measurement was taken from the Earth on one side of the Sun, and the second was taken half a year</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Parsec</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.parts_per_million">
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Parts per million</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.pascal">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">The pascal (symbol: Pa) is the SI derived unit of pressure, internal pressure, stress, Young's modulus and tensile strength, named after the French mathematician, physicist, inventor, writer, and philosopher Blaise Pascal. It is a measure of force per unit area, defined as one newton per square metre.\nOn Earth, standard atmospheric pressure is 101,325??Pa. In everyday life the pascal is perhaps best known from meteorological barometric pressure reports, where it occurs in the form of hectopascals (1??hPa ??? 100??Pa) or kilopascals (1??kPa ??? 1000??Pa). In other contexts, the kilopascal is commonly used, for example on bicycle tire labels. One hectopascal corresponds to about 0.1% of atmospheric pressure slightly above sea level; one kilopascal is about 1% of atmospheric pressure. One hectopascal is equivalent to one millibar; one standard atmosphere is exactly equal to 101.325??kPa or 1013.25??hPa or 101,325??Pa. The corresponding Imperial unit is pounds per square inch (psi).\nThe pascal can be expressed using SI derived units, or alternatively solely SI base units, as:\nWhere N is the newton, m is the metre, kg is the kilogram, and s is the second.\nThe unit is named after Blaise Pascal, the</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Pascal</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.pascal_second_measure">
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Pascal second</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.per_cubic_meter">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">Enumeration for the unit per Cubic Meter.</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">m^-3</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.per_mole">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">Enumeration for the unit per Mole.</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">mol^-1</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.percentage">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">In mathematics, a percentage is a way of expressing a number, especially a ratio, as a fraction of 100. The word is derived from the Latin per centum meaning ???by the hundred???. It is often denoted using the percent sign, ???%???, or the abbreviation ???pct.??? For example, 45% (read as ???forty-five percent???) is equal to 45/100, or 0.45. A related system which expresses a number as a fraction of 1000 uses the terms "per mil" and "millage".\nPercentages are used to express how large/small one quantity is, relative to another quantity. The first quantity usually represents a part of, or a change in, the second quantity, which should be greater than zero. For example, an increase of $??0.15 on a price of $??2.50 is an increase by a fraction of 0.15/2.50 = 0.06. Expressed as a percentage, this is therefore a 6% increase.\nAlthough percentages are usually used to express numbers between zero and one, any ratio can be expressed as a percentage. For instance, 111% is 1.11 and ???0.35% is ???0.0035. Although this is technically inaccurate as per the definition of percent, an alternative wording in terms of a change in an observed value is ???an increase/decrease by a factor of...??????\nIn Ancient Rome, long before</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Percentage</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.picometre">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">A picometre (American spelling: picometer; symbol pm) is a unit of length in the metric system, equal to one trillionth, i.e. (/1,000,000,000,000) of a metre, which is the current SI base unit of length. It can be written in scientific notation as 1??10??m, or as 1 E???12 m in engineering notation ??? both meaning 1 m / 1,000,000,000,000.\nIt equals a millionth of a micrometre (formerly called a micron), and was formerly called micromicron, stigma, or bicron. The symbol ???? was once used for it. It is also a hundredth of an angstrom, an internationally recognised but non-SI unit of length.\nThe picometre's length is of an order such that its application is almost entirely confined to particle physics and quantum physics. Atoms are between 62 and 520??pm in diameter. Smaller units still may be used to describe smaller particles (some of which are the components of atoms themselves), such as hadrons and the upper limits of possible size for fermion point particles.\nThe Laser Interferometer Space Antenna (LISA) probe had been planned to be launched in 2025 to directly detect gravitational waves and would have been able to measure relative displacements with a resolution of 20 picometres over a</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Picometre</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.pint_united_states">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">Unit of measure for pints in United States customary units</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Pint</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.pixel">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">In digital imaging, a pixel, or pel, (picture element) is a physical point in a raster image, or the smallest, addressable element in a display device; so it is the smallest, controllable element of a picture represented on the screen. The address of a pixel corresponds to its physical coordinates. LCD pixels are manufactured in a two-dimensional grid, and are often represented using dots or squares, but CRT pixels correspond to their timing mechanisms and sweep rates.\nEach pixel is a sample of an original image; more samples typically provide more accurate representations of the original. The intensity of each pixel is variable. In color image systems, a color is typically represented by three or four component intensities such as red, green, and blue, or cyan, magenta, yellow, and black.\nIn some contexts (such as descriptions of camera sensors), the term pixel is used to refer to a single scalar element of a multi-component representation (more precisely called a photosite in the camera sensor context, although the neologism sensel is sometimes used to describe the elements of a digital camera's sensor), while in others the term may refer to the entire set of such component</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Pixel</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.poise">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">Enumeration for the unit Poise.</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Poise</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.pound">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">The pound or pound-mass (abbreviations: lb, lbm, lbm, ??? ) is a unit of mass used in the imperial, United States customary and other systems of measurement. A number of different definitions have been used, the most common today being the international avoirdupois pound which is legally defined as exactly 0.45359237??kilograms.\nThe unit is descended from the Roman libra (hence the abbreviation "lb"); the name pound is a Germanic adaptation of the Latin phrase libra pondo, 'a pound weight'.\nUsage of the unqualified term pound reflects the historical conflation of mass and weight resulting from the near uniformity of gravity on Earth. This accounts for the modern distinguishing terms pound-mass and pound-force.\nThe United States and countries of the Commonwealth of Nations agreed upon common definitions for the pound and the yard. Since 1 July 1959, the international avoirdupois pound has been defined as exactly 0.45359237??kg.\nIn the United Kingdom, the use of the international pound was implemented in the Weights and Measures Act 1963.\nAn avoirdupois pound is equal to 16 avoirdupois ounces and to exactly 7,000 grains. The conversion factor between the kilogram and the international</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Pound</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.quart">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">Unit of measure for quart</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Quart</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.radian">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">Radian is the ratio between the length of an arc and its radius. The radian is the standard unit of angular measure, used in many areas of mathematics. The unit was formerly an SI supplementary unit, but this category was abolished in 1995 and the radian is now considered an SI derived unit. The SI unit of solid angle measurement is the steradian.\nThe radian is represented by the symbol "rad" or, more rarely, by the superscript c (for "circular measure"). For example, an angle of 1.2 radians would be written as "1.2 rad" or "1.2" (the second symbol is often mistaken for a degree: "1.2??"). As the ratio of two lengths, the radian is a "pure number" that needs no unit symbol, and in mathematical writing the symbol "rad" is almost always omitted. In the absence of any symbol radians are assumed, and when degrees are meant the symbol ?? is used.\nRadian describes the plane angle subtended by a circular arc as the length of the arc divided by the radius of the arc. One radian is the angle subtended at the center of a circle by an arc that is equal in length to the radius of the circle. More generally, the magnitude in radians of such a subtended angle is equal to the ratio of the arc</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Radian</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.radian_per_second">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">The radian per second (symbol: rad??s or rad/s) is the SI unit of rotational speed (angular velocity), commonly denoted by the Greek letter ?? (omega). The radian per second is also the unit of angular frequency.\nThe radian per second is defined as the change in the orientation of an object, in radians, every second.\nNote that because the radian is a dimensionless unit, the radian per second is dimensionally equivalent to the hertz???both are defined as one s. This means that great care must be taken to avoid confusing angular frequency ?? and frequency ??.\nOne of the important uses of the unit radian per second is in calculation of the power transmitted by a shaft. In the International System, widely used in physics and engineering, the power, p, delivered to the shaft is given by the product of ?? (in radians per second) times the torque, ??, in newton-meters applied to the shaft. Thus, p = ?? ??? ??, and the unit is the watt, with no numerical coefficient needed.\nIn other systems, the calculation is somewhat more complicated, because if one multiplies angular velocity in revolutions per minute (r.p.m.) times the torque in pound-feet, then a multiplicative constant is needed to give the</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Radian per second</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.radian_per_second_per_tesla">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">Enumeration for the unit Radian per Second per Tesla.</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">rads^-1T^-1</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.radian_per_second_squared">
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Radian per second squared</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.reciprocal_metre">
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Reciprocal metre</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.revolutions_per_minute">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">Enumeration of measurement unit representing revolutions per minute.</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Revolutions per minute</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.scoville_heat_unit">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">Enumeration representing the Scoville heat unit, which is a measurement of the pungency of foods or chemicals.</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">SHU</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.second">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">The second (symbol: s) is the base unit of time in the International System of Units (SI) and is also a unit of time in other systems of measurement (abbreviated s or sec). Between 1000 (when al-Biruni used seconds) and 1960 the second was defined as 1/86,400 of a mean solar day (that definition still applies in some astronomical and legal contexts). Between 1960 and 1967, it was defined in terms of the period of the Earth's orbit around the Sun in 1900, but it is now defined more precisely in atomic terms. </mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Second</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.siemens">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">The siemens (SI unit symbol: S) is the unit of electric conductance and electric admittance in the International System of Units (SI). Its symbol, "S" (upper case), should not be confused with the SI symbol "s" (lower case) which is used for second. Conductance and admittance are the reciprocals of resistance and impedance respectively, hence one siemens is equal to the reciprocal of one ohm, and is also referred to as the mho. The 14th General Conference on Weights and Measures approved the addition of the siemens as a derived unit in 1971.\nThe unit is named after Ernst Werner von Siemens. As with every SI unit whose name is derived from the proper name of a person, the first letter of its symbol is upper case (S). When an SI unit is spelled out in English, it should always begin with a lower case letter (siemens), except where any word would be capitalized. In English, the same form siemens is used both for the singular and plural.\nFor a conducting or semiconducting element with electrical resistance R, the conductance, G, is defined as\nwhere I is the electric current through the object and V is the voltage (electrical potential difference) across the object.\nThe unit siemens for</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Siemens</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.siemens_per_meter">
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Siemens per meter</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.sievert">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">The sievert (symbol: Sv) is the International System of Units (SI) derived unit of equivalent radiation dose, effective dose, and committed dose. Quantities that are measured in sieverts are designed to represent the stochastic biological effects of ionizing radiation. The sievert should not be used to express the unmodified absorbed dose of radiation energy, which is a clear physical quantity measured in grays. To enable consideration of biological effects, further calculations must be performed to convert absorbed dose into effective dose, the details of which depend on the biological context. This can be far more complicated than just multiplying by a weighting factor.\nThe sievert is of fundamental importance in radiation dosimetry, and is named after Rolf Maximilian Sievert, a Swedish medical physicist renowned for work on radiation dosage measurement and research into the biological effects of radiation. One sievert equals 100 rem, an older unit of measurement still in widespread use. One sievert carries with it a 5.5% chance of eventually developing cancer. Doses greater than 1 sievert received over a short time period are likely to cause radiation poisoning, possibly leading</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Sievert</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.solar_luminosity">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">The solar luminosity, L???, is a unit of radiant flux (power emitted in the form of photons) conventionally used by astronomers to measure the luminosity of stars. One solar luminosity is equal to the current accepted luminosity of the Sun, which is 3.839??10??W, or 3.839??10??erg/s. The value is slightly higher, 3.939??10??W (equivalent to 4.382??10??kg/s or 1.9??10??M???/d) if the solar neutrino radiation is included as well as electromagnetic radiation. The Sun is a weakly variable star and its luminosity therefore fluctuates. The major fluctuation is the eleven-year solar cycle (sunspot cycle), which causes a periodic variation of about ??0.1%. Any other variation over the last 200???300 years is thought to be much smaller than this.\nThe solar luminosity is related to the solar irradiance measured at the Earth or by satellites in Earth orbit. The mean irradiance at the top of the Earth's atmosphere is sometimes known as the solar constant, I???. Irradiance is defined as power per unit area, so the solar luminosity (total power emitted by the Sun) is the irradiance received at the Earth (solar constant) multiplied by the area of the sphere whose radius is the mean distance between the Earth and</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Solar luminosity</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.solar_mass">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">The solar mass () is a standard unit of mass in astronomy, used to indicate the masses of other stars, as well as clusters, nebulae and galaxies. It is equal to the mass of the Sun, about two nonillion kilograms:\nThis is about 332,950 times the mass of the Earth or 1,048 times the mass of Jupiter.\nBecause the Earth follows an elliptical orbit around the Sun, the solar mass can be computed from the equation for the orbital period of a small body orbiting a central mass. Based upon the length of the year, the distance from the Earth to the Sun (an astronomical unit or AU), and the gravitational constant (G), the mass of the Sun is given by:\nThe value of the gravitational constant was derived from 1798 measurements by Henry Cavendish using a torsion balance. The value obtained differed only by about 1% from the modern value. The diurnal parallax of the Sun was accurately measured during the transits of Venus in 1761 and 1769, yielding a value of 9??? (compared to the present 1976 value of 8.794148???). When the value of the diurnal parallax is known, the distance to the Sun can be determined from the geometry of the Earth.\nThe first person to estimate the mass of the Sun was Isaac Newton.</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Solar mass</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.solar_radius">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">Solar radius is a unit of distance used to express the size of stars in astronomy equal to the current radius of the Sun:\nThe solar radius is approximately 695,500 kilometres (432,450 miles) or about 110 times the radius of the Earth, or 10 times the average radius of Jupiter. It varies slightly from pole to equator due to its rotation, which induces an oblateness of order 10 parts per million. See 1 gigametre for similar distances.\nThe SOHO spacecraft was used to measure the diameter of the Sun by timing transits of Mercury across the surface during 2003 and 2006. The result was a measured radius of 696,342??????65 kilometres (432,687??????40 miles).</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Solar radius</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.source">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">Property relating an mso:type.unit to the organization.organization that published or is the source of the data.</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Source</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.property" />
    <mso:type.property.expected_type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/organization.organization" />
    <mso:type.property.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.square_coulomb_per_newton_per_square_meter">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">Enumeration for the unit Square Coulomb per Newton per Square Meter.</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">C^2N^-1m^2</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.square_coulomb_square_meter_per_joule">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">Enumeration for the unit Square Coulomb Square Meter per Joule.</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">C^2m^2J^-1</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.square_degrees">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">A non-SI unit that is the square of the measure of angular degree.</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Square Degrees</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.square_kilometer">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">Square kilometre, symbol km, is a decimal multiple of the SI unit of surface area, the square metre, one of the SI derived units. 1??km is equal to:\nIt is also approximately equal to:\nConversely:\n2.47 acres/ha\nNote: "km" means (km), square kilometre or kilometre squared and not k(m), kilo???square metre. For example, 3??km is equal to 3??(1,000m) = 3,000,000??m, not 3,000??m.\nNote also that if a piece of land, say a large park, is described as five kilometres square, that means it has the shape of a square, each side of the square being five kilometres long. This means that the park has an area of twenty-five square kilometres (and not five square kilometres).\nTopographical map grids are worked out in metres, with the grid lines being 1,000 metres apart.\nIn each case, the grid lines enclose one square kilometre.\nParks come in all sizes; a few are almost exactly one square kilometre in area. Here are some examples:\nSome golf courses cover more than a square kilometre; many cover less ground. Here are examples of golf courses of 1 square kilometre:</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Square kilometer</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.square_meter">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">The square metre (British spelling) or square meter (American spelling) is the SI derived unit of area, with symbol m (33A1 in Unicode). It is defined as the area of a square whose sides measure exactly one metre. The square metre is derived from the SI base unit of the metre, which in turn is defined as the length of the path travelled by light in absolute vacuum during a time interval of 1/299,792,458 of a second.\nAdding and subtracting SI prefixes creates multiples and submultiples; however, as the unit is squared, the order of magnitude difference between units doubles from their comparable linear units. For example, a kilometre is one thousand times the length of a metre, but a square kilometre is one million times the area of a square metre.\nThe square metre may be used with all SI prefixes used with the meter.\nA square metre is equal to:</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Square meter</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.square_meter_per_second">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">Enumeration for the unit Squared Meter per Second.</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">m^2/s</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.steradian">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">The steradian (symbol: sr) is the SI unit of solid angle. It is used to describe two-dimensional angular spans in three-dimensional space, analogous to the way in which the radian describes angles in a plane. The name is derived from the Greek stereos for "solid" and the Latin radius for "ray, beam".\nThe steradian, like the radian, is dimensionless because 1 sr = m??m = 1. It is useful, however, to distinguish between dimensionless quantities of different nature, so in practice the symbol "sr" is used where appropriate, rather than the derived unit "1" or no unit at all. For example, radiant intensity can be measured in watts per steradian (W??sr). The steradian was formerly an SI supplementary unit, but this category was abolished from the SI in 1995 and the steradian is now considered an SI derived unit.\nA steradian can be defined as the solid angle subtended at the center of a unit sphere by a unit area on its surface. For a general sphere of radius r, any portion of its surface with area A = r subtends one steradian.\nSince A = r, it corresponds to the area of a spherical cap (A = 2??rh) (wherein h stands for the "height" of the cap), and the relationship h/r = 1/(2??) holds.</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Steradian</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.tablespoon">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">Unit of measure for tablespoon</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.teaspoon">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">Unit of measure for teaspoon</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Teaspoon</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.tesla">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">Enumeration for the unit Tesla.</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Tesla</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.tesla_measure">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">The tesla (symbol T) is the SI derived unit of magnetic flux density, commonly denoted as B, (which is also known as "magnetic field"). One tesla is equal to one weber per square meter, and it was defined in 1960 in honour of the Serbian inventor, physicist, and electrical engineer Nikola Tesla. The strongest fields encountered from permanent magnets are from Halbach spheres which can be over 5??T.\nA particle carrying a charge of 1 coulomb and passing through a magnetic field of 1 tesla at a speed of 1 meter per second perpendicular to said field experiences a force of 1 newton, according to the Lorentz force law. As an SI derived unit, the tesla can also be expressed as\n(The 5th equivalent is in SI base units).\nUnits used:\nIn the production of the Lorentz force, the difference between these types of field is that a force from a magnetic field on a charged particle is generally due to the charged particle's movement while the force imparted by an electric field on a charged particle is not due to the charged particle's movement. This may be appreciated by looking at the units for each. The unit of electric field in the MKS system of units is newtons per coulomb, N/C, while the</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Tesla</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.tesla_meter_per_ampere">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">Enumeration for the unit Tesla Meter per Ampere.</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">T m/A</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.tonne">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">The tonne (SI unit symbol: t) is a metric system unit of mass equal to 1,000??kilograms (2,204.6 pounds). It is a non-SI unit accepted for use with SI. To avoid confusion with the ton, it is also known as the metric tonne and metric ton in the United States and occasionally in the United Kingdom. In SI units and prefixes, the tonne is a megagram (Mg), a rarely-used symbol, easily confused with mg, for milligram.\nIn the U.S., the National Institute of Standards and Technology supports the symbol "t" for the tonne. The abbreviation "mt" or "MT" is also used in the U.S.\nThe SI unit symbol for the tonne is "t". Abbreviations for "tonne" ("metric ton" and "metric tonne") include "T", "mT", "MT", and "mt" (especially in the combination "mmt" or "MMT" for "million metric tons"), and "Te" (particularly in the offshore and nuclear industries). SI has no abbreviations for SI units, only symbols, and some of the abbreviations in use are actually SI symbols for other units: "T" is the SI symbol for the tesla and "Mt" is the SI symbol for megatonne.\nIn France and the English-speaking countries that are predominantly metric, tonne is the usual formal usage in writing, usually pronounced the same</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Tonne</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.twenty_foot_equivalent_unit">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">The twenty-foot equivalent unit (often TEU or teu) is an inexact unit of cargo capacity often used to describe the capacity of container ships and container terminals. It is based on the volume of a 20-foot-long (6.1??m) intermodal container, a standard-sized metal box which can be easily transferred between different modes of transportation, such as ships, trains and trucks.\nOne TEU represents the cargo capacity of a standard intermodal container, 20 feet (6.1??m) long and 8 feet (2.44??m) wide. There is a lack of standardisation in regards to height, ranging between 4??feet 3??inches (1.30??m) and 9??feet 6??inches (2.90??m), with the most common height being 8??feet 6??inches (2.59??m). Also, it is common to designate 45-foot (13.7??m) containers as 2 TEU, rather than 2.25 TEU.\nAs the TEU is an inexact unit, it cannot be converted precisely into other units. The related unit forty-foot equivalent unit (often FEU or feu) however is defined as two TEU. The most common dimensions for a 20-foot (6.1??m) container are 20 feet (6.1??m) long, 8 feet (2.44??m) wide, and 8??feet 6??inches (2.59??m) high, for a volume of 1,360 cubic feet (39??m). However, both 9-foot-6-inch-tall (2.90??m) High cube and</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Twenty-foot equivalent unit</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.volt">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">The volt (symbol: V) is the SI derived unit for electric potential, electric potential difference, and electromotive force. The volt is named in honor of the Italian physicist Alessandro Volta (1745???1827), who invented the voltaic pile, possibly the first chemical battery.\nA single volt is defined as the difference in electric potential across a wire when an electric current of one ampere dissipates one watt of power. It is also equal to the potential difference between two parallel, infinite planes spaced 1 meter apart that create an electric field of 1 newton per coulomb. Additionally, it is the potential difference between two points that will impart one joule of energy per coulomb of charge that passes through it. It can be expressed in terms of SI units as follows:\nIt can also be written using only the SI base units m, kg, s, and A as:\nBetween 1990 and 1997, the volt was calibrated using the Josephson effect for exact voltage-to-frequency conversion, combined with cesium-133 time reference, as decided by the 18th General Conference on Weights and Measures. The following value for the Josephson constant is used:\nThis is typically used with an array of several thousand or tens</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Volt</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.volt_per_metre">
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Volt per metre</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.volt_per_square_meter">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">Enumeration for the unit Volt per Square Meter.</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">V/m^2</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.watt">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">The watt (??/??w??t/ WOT; symbol: W) is a derived unit of power in the International System of Units (SI), named after the Scottish engineer James Watt (1736???1819). The unit, defined as one joule per second, measures the rate of energy conversion or transfer.\nThe watt is named after the Scottish scientist James Watt for his contributions to the development of the steam engine. The unit was recognized by the Second Congress of the British Association for the Advancement of Science in 1882. The 11th General Conference on Weights and Measures in 1960 adopted it for the measurement of power into the International System of Units (SI).\nThe femtowatt is equal to one quadrillionth (10) of a watt. Technologically important powers that are measured in femtowatts are typically found in reference(s) to radio and radar receivers. For example, meaningful FM tuner performance figures for sensitivity, quieting and signal-to-noise require that the RF energy applied to the antenna input be specified. These input levels are often stated in dBf (decibels referenced to 1 femtowatt). This is 0.2739 microvolt across a 75 ohm load or 0.5477 microvolt across a 300 ohm load; the specification takes into</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Watt</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.watt_hour">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">An enumeration value for watt-hours, the number of watts used/generated per hour.</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Watt-Hour</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.watt_per_metre_per_kelvin">
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Watt per meter per kelvin</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.watt_per_square_meter_per_kelvin_to_the_fourth">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">Enumeration for the unit Watt per Square Meter per Kelvin to the Fourth.</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Wm^-2K^-4</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.watt_per_square_metre">
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Watt per square metre</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.watt_per_square_metre_per_steradian">
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Watt per square metre per steradian</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.watt_per_steradian">
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Watt per steradian</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.watt_square_meter">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">Enumeration for the unit Watt Square Meter.</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">W m^2</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.watt_square_meter_per_steradian">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">Enumeration for the unit Watt Square Meter per Steradian.</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">W m^2/sr</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.weber">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">In physics, the weber (symbol: Wb; ??/??ve??b??r/, /??w??b??r/, or /??wi??b??r/) is the SI unit of magnetic flux. A flux density of one Wb/m (one weber per square meter) is one tesla.\nThe weber is named for the German physicist Wilhelm Eduard Weber (1804???1891).\nThe weber may be defined in terms of Faraday's law, which relates a changing magnetic flux through a loop to the electric field around the loop. A change in flux of one weber per second will induce an electromotive force of one volt (produce an electric potential difference of one volt across two open-circuited terminals).\nOfficially,\nWeber (unit of magnetic flux) ??? The weber is the magnetic flux which, linking a circuit of one turn, would produce in it an electromotive force of 1 volt if it were reduced to zero at a uniform rate in 1 second.\nIn SI base units, the dimensions of the weber are (kg??m)/(s??A). The weber is commonly expressed in terms of other derived units as the Tesla-square meter (T??m), volt-seconds (V??s), or joules per ampere (J/A).\n\nThis SI unit is named after Wilhelm Eduard Weber. As with every International System of Units (SI) unit whose name is derived from the proper name of a person, the first letter of its</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Weber</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.week">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">One of the 52 periods into which a year is divided.</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Week</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.yard">
    <mso:type.object.description xml:lang="en">A yard (abbreviation: yd) is a unit of length in several different systems including United States customary units, Imperial units and the former English units. It is equal to 3 feet or 36 inches. Under an agreement in 1959 between Australia, Canada, New Zealand, South Africa, the United Kingdom and the United States, the yard (known as the "international yard" in the United States) was legally defined to be exactly 0.9144 metres. Prior to that date, the legal definition of the yard when expressed in terms of metric units varied slightly from country to country.\nFor purposes of measuring cloth, the early yard was divided by the binary method into two, four, eight and sixteen parts. The two most common divisions were the fourth and sixteenth parts. The quarter of a yard was known as the "quarter" without further qualification, while the sixteenth of a yard was called a nail. The eighth of a yard was sometimes called a finger, but was more commonly referred to simply as an eighth of a yard, while the half-yard was called "half a yard."\nOther units related to the yard, but not specific to cloth measurement: two yards are a fathom, a quarter of a yard (when not referring to cloth) is a</mso:type.object.description>
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Yard</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
  <rdf:Description rdf:about="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit.zoom_factor">
    <mso:type.object.name xml:lang="en">Zoom factor</mso:type.object.name>
    <mso:type.object.type rdf:resource="http://knowledge.microsoft.com/mso/type.unit" />
  </rdf:Description>
</rdf:RDF>